<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="dino_names">
        <item>Brachiosaurus</item>
        <item>Carnotaurus</item>
        <item>Giganotosaurus</item>
        <item>Pentaceratops</item>
        <item>Parasaurolophus</item>
        <item>Rajasaurus</item>
        <item>Styracosaurus</item>
        <item>Spinosaurus</item>
        <item>Minmi</item>
        <item>Deinonychus</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dino_info">
        <item>
            This drawing shows the possible appearance of Brachiosaurus, a Sauropod dinosaur from
            the late Jurassic Period (around 150 million years ago). The Brachiosaurus was a herbivore
            (plant eater) and lived in North America.
        </item>
        <item>
            This CGI drawing shows the possible appearance of Carnotaurus, a dinosaur that lived at
            the end of the Cretaceous Period (around 66 million years ago). Carnotaurus was a meat
            eating dinosaur (carnivore) with small arms and fingers that did not move.
        </item>
        <item>
            This CGI drawing shows the possible appearance of Giganotosaurus, a dinosaur from the
            late Cretaceous Period (around 100 million years ago). Giganotosaurus was a carnivore
            (meat eater) that was even bigger than the more well known Tyrannosaurus rex. Its name
            means \'giant southern lizard\'.
        </item>
        <item>
            This drawing shows the possible appearance of Pentaceratops, a dinosaur from the late
            Cretaceous Period (around 75 million years ago). Pentaceratops (meaning \'five horned face\')
            is related to the Triceratops (meaning \'three horned face\' and like other Ceratopsid
            dinosaurs, ate plants. It weighed around 5500 kg (13000 lb) and reached around 8 metres
            (27 feet) in length.
        </item>
        <item>
            This CGI drawing shows the possible appearance of Parasaurolophus, a dinosaur from the
            late Cretaceous Period (around 75 million years ago). Parasaurolophus were plant eaters
            (herbivores) that lived in North America.
        </item>
        <item>
            This CGI drawing shows the possible appearance of Rajasaurus (which interestingly means
            \'prince\' or \'princely lizard\'), a dinosaur from the late Cretaceous Period (around 70
            million years ago). Found in India, it featured a unique head crest and measured around
            8 metres (26 feet) in length.
        </item>
        <item>
            This drawing shows the possible appearance of Styracosaurus, a dinosaur from the late
            Cretaceous Period (around 75 million years ago). The name Styracosaurus means \'spiked
            lizard\' and refers to the horns coming from its neck frill as well as the horns on its
            cheeks and larger horn coming from its nose, which could have been up to 60cm in length.
            Styracosaurus was a large, bulky dinosaur that ate plants (herbivore).
        </item>
        <item>
            This CGI drawing shows the possible appearance of Spinosaurus, a dinosaur from the
            Cretaceous Period (around 100 million years ago). With huge spines growing from its back
            and the biggest size of any meat eating (carnivorous) dinosaur, the Spinosaurus must
            have been one scary looking dinosaur.
        </item>
        <item>
            This drawing shows the possible appearance of Minmi, a small dinosaur from the early
            Cretaceous Period (around 116 million years ago). Minmi was an armoured dinosaur and
            like other Ankylosaurs, was a herbivore (plant eater). It was named Minmi after remains
            were found near the Minmi Crossing in Australia.
        </item>
        <item>
            This CGI drawing shows the possible appearance of Deinonychus, a dinosaur from the early
            Cretaceous Period (around 110 million years ago). Deinonychus was from the same family of
            dinosaurs as the Velociraptor and its name means \'terrible claw\'.
        </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>